<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hamzah Chaudhry</title><link>https://hamzahch.com/</link><description>Recent content on Hamzah Chaudhry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2020 Hamzah Chaudhry</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 20:14:35 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hamzahch.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quantity Over Quality?</title><link>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/quantity-over-quality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 19:54:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/quantity-over-quality/</guid><description>Since the advent of modern corporations, a company with a market cap in the billions and even trillions is not a thing of the past anymore. Large corporations have been pushing the boundaries of capitalism to make every last penny in profits.</description></item><item><title>An Omnipresent Risk to Our Privacies</title><link>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/omnipresent-risk-to-privacy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 19:52:31 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/omnipresent-risk-to-privacy/</guid><description>Privacy has become a contentious issue in the age of the Internet and it will be ever-prevalent as technology continues to progress. The COVID-19 pandemic has only shown glimpses of what lengths governments are willing to go to compromise their citizens’ privacy in the face of “national emergency.</description></item><item><title>The Game of Gaming – Will it Pay Off?</title><link>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/game-of-gaming/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 19:47:01 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/game-of-gaming/</guid><description>Gaming’s recent rise to mainstream culture has offered media channels a new source of revenue. Esports and competitive gaming has cultivated an immense following — enough for it to be featured on national TV. With the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic, the entertainment industry has been looking for alternatives to fill the void left by typical programming.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Productivity or Virtual Boundaries?</title><link>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/virtual-productivity-virtual-boundaries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 19:41:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hamzahch.com/blog/2020/virtual-productivity-virtual-boundaries/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic has shifted our entire worldview; the activities we are routinely used to — eating out, interacting with coworkers, attending classes — have meanwhile ceased, except for the collective push towards remote working. Businesses and schools alike have enabled their employees and students, respectively, to communicate via online messaging and conferencing platforms.</description></item></channel></rss>